Live live
live.
live
Live
.
Is he.
Going to get too many look like you keep.
Your somewhere all going west he jumps
so you're good with your back is not bothering
us I'm interested in his books. Like
beer. Now you know the
complete. Shakespeare and
German I can. Be moved tonight
or desperate. Dr Toby
just be across the border before dawn but
we have had orders not to break interest
house and high chair and been outside
in weeks if you are but it's no trouble
bespeaks look at the moment you must be
very careful if we can't break in he want
to come out and if ya need something as
big as he needs to be bomb site it is
basically that the interested in that
same people you use to make forged space
papers and he believes they come from him
you know gentlemen the price is much too
low I could not place against
it in some way a book with such
a place Evelyn juiced up to build
a community to my shop is
vastly. Increased in D.C.
And mail instead of peace mark
the. Band that's going to
just head. To Shanghai doesn't try to take
Dr Bill from under our very eyes. Yes
it is stupid Bunting amateur detective His
name is Holmes or some such foolishness
you could never escape from Switzerland the
life of quick let me thrown out of here
and watch from a signal from Dr Toby
swindle but gentlemen you promised to buy
a bunch of my book I thought I don't
know stop bothering us and not so great
a price and here is R.T.C.
Are you are going to shut up shop open for
me leave on your back after dinner was
a very bad thing are now an added.
Complication I think I am prepared for
some. English I
hate those richest Calm
yourself my dear brother in
a short time there will
be only one language.
Evening. A hint here something interesting
sanctity books I thought you might like
to see these coming.
Singeing the house quickly
get the car have to look at any other
fellow expert to talk about Pam said to the
hero of this Holmes is still you Steve.
What are you doing. I am sorry
but for months every move I have
made has been watched I am not
a coward Mr Home they won't watch any
more tonight than ten Thank you forcibly
across the German border and why don't
we wait here doing nothing like rats in
a trap I'm going to help my doctor too
about this not only escaped their trap but
we should also take the cheese away with
this but the top four sections of your
bomb site fit inside these bundles tomes
although I must confess that I shy to the
vault of disembarking and concrete steps
Charles Dickens but you cannot hide me in
a hollow book. Oh I'm sorry that my good
friend Dr Watson isn't here to explain to
you but my preparation
is another slipshod.
Step and I think why do you call my servants
go seven steps but tonight they assume
you wrote the present Dr Joe Bill and I
don't friend the bookseller Holmes it is so
simple as the obvious always if you are
simple but now we must leap step on the
next act.
Stiffened etiquette for the excellent
cookies in the shuttle has been pulled
completely. The students are leading them
into the next treat but what would happen
to define an attic now they don't want
it I didn't get it that. Way scare.
Only.
To want to take the Nazis on
caught on the deck oneself to lose
a hand. When
you think you made them believe you are
a harmless all bookseller
as I've always felt that
a better knowledge of the
classics might come in handy.
But how can we get across the border and
for bronze there's no need to get guns.
There's been none of the rotten apples
bangers waiting but I suppose you could kind
of place.
How long before we arrived in London
in a very few minutes the passing of
a dove Thanks.
We'll have to get used to
London blackouts not until.
Dr Watsons be on time to follow. Up what
are we going to do with these problem is I
mean I'm pretty sure my dear Dr Bell.
You are going to keep them here I've always
believed in the theory and originally
protected by example the American right.
But the best place to hide anything is
where everyone can see
it yes but if you were
a member no doubt the first story
that. The missive in question.
Was always an Plainview.
And sometimes.
Scotland Yard quick. Oh my
goodness. What I mean is this has
a. Price Mr Holmes was home and I was not
going to see him again. Oh do
you want. Oh yeah sure Scotland
Yard and prisoners going to stick Oh
you know we only it was take sometimes
not well if we didn't you'd be out of
a job. Dr Kobi this is my kind of associated
And as you may have observed my watch
dog Dr Watson How do you do it or how do
you do Dr Joe but I'm not doing films yet
it was easy for me but I
think a way no What's
a doctor told them one of them
asking a question physics an I.Q.
Thirty nine idea what it was only one Dr
Toby Oh without Mr Holmes there would have
been no Dr Toby I am afraid but I thought
you were living in America and I've been
working in Switzerland for the past two
years and Holmes got you out in the nick of
time there was not
a point you overlooked every contingency
was foreseen and provided for it was
magnificent Thank you doctor the problem
is not without its interesting point is
that anything you would like Mr Holmes like
it is has been going to bed now he gave
me enough right dish to
plant their heads and
a good night's rest was quite right you
can blame me for jumping to conclusions I
did he looked like
a broken down musician homes why didn't
you take your foot over there I never did
think much of this dressing up business
before it's necessary I assure you that the
shop was closing argue. This shot comes
I want to speak sir John Bailey please
raise your belly There's a fellow Pedregon
for Blackheath Yes WATSON Oh I was
a Reginald I'm speaking yes from big
a street I have Dr Toby with me
over thank you very well then I
mean how often are. And there's been no
delay on the arrangements original to have
a test tomorrow morning I suggested only
cabinet ministers and your best aviation
experts be present naturally once an
eye doctor troubling your cat give him
a sedative this is been a
strenuous business and he has
a long day ahead of him again tomorrow seven
homes of course he should sleep in my
bedroom I'll keep watch to you return thank
you it is not necessary to God me I am
quite safe now safe Dr Bell
I wouldn't count on it for
a second but Mr great deal may depend on
your safety and the enemy understands that
just as well as we do good night.
You cannot props and of course
a couple of these and you'll
sleep peacefully through
a bit back you better start and rested ones
you'll find yourself fast asleep in the
middle of taking off your trousers Well
acid over here keep an eye on things. If
you're nervous call out Good night doctor
good night doctor. Posting the same
thing as a doctor but not
a doctor. I'm
trying to find
a home. In
.
Now. Yes I just write about an outcome it
is most important that I see what parts
No no I cannot explain. It is
now five minutes past midnight
I didn't want to get back.
Oh but I don't have to tell you how
much this means to us we should know
a great deal more about the bomb site after
the demonstrations original the office
have
a pretty good idea of the value of the two
of album sites just as the Nazis have
further so if you'd care
to place Dr Toby L.
Under the protection of
Scotland Yard and turn on
a row now that what the necessity I saw
personally deliver Dr Dobelle to your
representatives on Salzburg plane in plenty
of time to demonstration Thank you good
night to Reginald Good
luck Mr Holmes. For.
The opinion.
That Abel E.
Flat be right at the county I'll
wait here until he comes out.
Is that with the Americans quote. It is
more serious than you could possibly
election good.
Luck and no thank you darling I must get
back before they miss Britain separated
for so long I couldn't be out of anything
sit tight if again I want to work with
you and I want to know every minute where
you are even for you to know the details
of my mission in London is to
sign your death or if you are
a real danger I want to see you
there is one thing you can do.
God bless and if anything happens to
me see that it reaches the hands of Mr
Sherlock Holmes this year now
comes I pray I never have to live
a. Little
.
You got away your I think.
I think so. Must've been
a rough sense of lack of
those but has become quite
a nuisance. I say you better come with me
and have that fixed up right here that's
been on my arm that's.
One way car where if you look at me and
he's gone that's impossible it's even my
little old car if anything's
happened to him tell.
All right it has nothing
Yes I don't hear much of
a look. There's not
a bear who patched up the police Dr Yes
it looks you've been attacked obvious and
either What's the trouble. You suspect the
woman of the range of the track woman
but woman she's blonde five foot six bullet
and very affectionate for her if not
a prolonged time it was attacked after
leaving that apartment homes how do you know
there's a face powder on
your character as you have
a heightened affection for you you were
held her close before departing to the home
it's all there for the trained eye to read
Watson but look here why I couldn't even
detect only way to the woman's
apartment the mark of a blow has
a race some of the powder Obviously if the
attack came first the part it would have
remained understood in
the full look that was
a guess I never I guess what. You have
read the dipstick from your face with
a handkerchief you're not in your hand and
that amount of lipstick never came from
a pair of thin lips the
blood on her show good
Mr Holmes I am glad you are on my side
well in that case you will desist from
disobeying my orders and slipping out
while ya buddy God steeps his watch away
going to happen again home I was sitting
in front of the family I don't know right
so I don't know can you describe
your assailant. I never saw him
a great figure came at
me in the dock I felt
a stunning blow on my head in and instantly
fingers were at my throat but you must
have noticed something about
him think man I think
a little consequence to you may
mean a great deal to meet wait wait
a moment there was one thing long
fingers at my throat like steel
and then and that and odor and the drug
like go to the drug opium that is it I
am sure of it now. I suggest
we get the remains of
a good night's sleep remember the test
takes place tomorrow morning on Salzburg
play.
The principle of Delta two bills devise
involves the use of three sonic beings that
likes and that appears to be
a fix. That
.
Will.
Well gentlemen that
a load would sink in to ship in that way
we must consider the possibility of good
putting I don't like it. I like to see
another try at it so what I. Wanted to
try again so. He's coming into
position now isn't. That
all the polls now suck.
Well gentlemen how do you like
about the site not mob revenue. In
Specialist John Yes Originally. I hope
Scotland Yard is taking every precaution to
God up the Dobelle and his equipment to
plain clothes men ride with him in his coat
and four others following another one so.
He's coming to my office in what order
through the lens which
I was not gentlemen.
Here you gentlemen to listen to the second
mazing performance I said it was not. It
was magnificent Dr Toby magnificent I am
glad we had such ideal conditions for the
test I wouldn't have believed it if I
hadn't seen it myself we've been through
enough of them thank goodness he's safe
now you brought child operates with you
know so much no I did not but if I know
what it must be lodged in the most
impregnable boat in this building until
we're ready to start manufacture I have
orange for
a little office of my own I intend to
supervise the manufacture myself but you you
offered it to our government for our use
everything Mr Holmes has done has been
with that idea and you I still offered it
to your government but no one else will
know the secrets involved I have
to plan to got my invention
a plan as intricate as the bomb site itself
if you imagine for one moment please I
will not change my mind such I am
taking the matter into my own hands.
Just first do you propose to do Dr Bell I
am sorry I cannot reveal the details of
my plan for the crisis do
you think that's wise at
a great tension and I cannot change my
decision I show work independently.
Can't you persuade him Oh but supposing
something should happen to your job to job
you know there's only been one attempt on
your life and homes especially the right
back wasn't there is no use discussing
it gentlemen my mind is made up Scotland
Yard already doubled the guard
a better doctor in fact quadruple it that
is just what I do not wish done inspector
that would only draw attention
to my activities. Good day to.
Just the same all of my memoir King him in
a moment from now on no way to show it
must not offend Dr Bell you must remember
that he as
a citizen of Switzerland is under no
obligation to give us his invention we must do
as he asks why don't you agree HOLMES To
be sure said Reginald I'm not officially
connected with the government in nine ten
to remain on the case good that is if
Inspector list dragged us mind or until Mr
Bush were always led away viewing around
thank you you can put those who are in
a. Huff
I am in trusting this to you all because
first of all you out of Swiss and second
there is no doubt in my
mind of your ability I'm
a doctor told Bill I have divided the
mechanism of my invention into four units
each is meaningless without the others you
have delivered the other three yes no
wonder myself knows the identity of the
four scientists working on the four units
their names are not even known to each
other I think I understand from what you
tell me it will be easy to reproduce to
unit assigned to me in any quantity you
wish I knew I could rely on you I will get
in touch with you as soon as I have made
the rest of my acquaintance I don't know
the back door if you please Professor.
Of law. Allow
us to start oh no well.
When it is home just as I feared the strands
men report that the bell is missing.
Yes I was afraid of is how long has he been
missing back again since you walked out
of your office yesterday if you don't give
me the address of this precise I'm going
to waste so much time finding an. Empty the
bomb sites gone I didn't expect to find
it yes original this is
a pretty mess if you know this is going
to have to lead to defeat and to do
something about it you can rely on
Holmes implicit to Sorrento to balance
government have no no no sway and serves
me right but listening to that crack
brained idea of his he just mistrust
strategy men and they went leaving him here
alone and on God homes if anything has
happened to to overlook his invention fallen
into the hands of Germany it would be
a major disaster for Christmas wrapping he
did his Christmas shopping in plenty of
time curious do you know serving home sent
per few as I noticed at the moment into
the room. One of the rare instances and
but expensive that woman again and ugly.
Given specular start so I comes calling so
home just fine I was stumped first time
I heard him call for help call for
help indeed he did just beginning is
investigation this God This is
Holmes check the records and trace
a call made on my private telephone to Baker
Street approximately twelve o'clock on
the night of October arrival in London
finally stumped. Yes I started but it.
Shall not be able
a study for some Georgia Street let Be
excellent to start I go.
Where it is Dr Toby Oh. I
can't tell you if you won't tell me I don't
know how many Christmas packages did
you take them to seventy five he dismantled
his bomb site infected units and four
of the boxes that correct. How to.
Hello yes this is Miss A Billy quiet
for someone must have stolen
it on Richmond bypass Yes
yes I know him to have
it removed Yes It wants.
Now I can be frank with you Mr Holmes Dr
Bell has disappeared they found my car
a malignant bypass like I loaned it to him
last night for what purpose miserably he
wouldn't tell me but he said that if
anything should happen to him. I don't give
you that hope because then he must be
expected something yes because envelope has
been opened and resealed but that isn't
possible it hasn't been out of my hands.
We meet again Mr Holmes I don't know why
that's not the message it isn't even the
same paper I saw Dr Bell drawled It all
sets of figures what kind of figures. They
looked like little dancing men don't sing
then it's curious who's been in this
apartment since Dr develop trust of the
temple of your care and no one I've had no
visitors think possibly a
tradesmen No only that one for
a few minutes and that one workman he came
to fix my lights which he couldn't have
possibly to send for him and no lights
went out and soon afterwards he knocked at
my door and told me the porter had sent him
up that's where he worked but he wasn't
alone in this one more than five minutes
and he did fix the lights they went on
again with switches and been touched the
paint still covers the screw heads. You
simply through the mean speech in the
basement pretended to work on this one Dr
a few moments and I've come to some of
the main switch back on but in those few
minutes if you get a look
at his face you know only
a glance now I will as he kept
his face about it but he was
a large man yes he was not his eyes he did
confirm over the people's homes you can
remember now his eyes they
were like a snake's is
a lead Dr Toby Ellis being held by one of
the most brilliant men in the history of
crime come on Watson but in a
moment it was because I was
a bit. Go
with you you were going on mission wasn't
going to take a seal no to inspect
a star and when you search on the horizon
up ascension for him I submit him to find
me the character of
a murderous Lask I wanted his employ and
no man I may add is still in jail but
after all these years make no
mistake but to me this is not
a duel going to mix with the crew but single
minded Gestapo cannot use our great is
problem with England is the stake
and I'm tag honest Professor I'm
going to you've got to be
a. One seed behind both but if you're
going to try to have my members of these
adventures the end Mario to an excellent
fact of art something very very.
We must arrange that it isn't my reality
who is left to write to memoirs.
Why not see ride at all I want to
see rises early. On in my office
you guys if I saw my supervisor
in my seat rise early in the on
line she rises on the rise in
line on the sea rises merrily in.
My office rises.
At.
That.
Time she. Come see me. For no I'm saying
I do. You mean war fresh been
in jail and she I you know
I heard from the watch list you just
screen instead if you. You know
I'm
a mighty I know my propeller twenty
three you know it came time to you
know where I live it changed and I
never I got to the bottom of it.
Five ten times on nothing I lie and even
go to the wiring one time I still ask you
about for what you want
and that. Will make
a good bargain. At
that. Well you know the name that
I knew was caught in falling
when I was still in the alley tell you I
can digest Brady's copy and shop and you
can tell you where that bright head is at
this funny moment if you have come to go
maybe. If you are a liar Mr
I'll come along with yeah A.Z.
Mighty easy. Follow me.
Governor I mean I had no need
for to have you all the way.
Up. Thank you.
There is this bloke in depth actually
Stephen for days good money to spend for
information. To.
Watch a woman out a give me a year five
pounds to bring him to someone like
a tell him that we're about to you know
you're not telling me I kept on throat
cost and the five and five
more. You know Pam may come
on. Come on Pam.
I'll tell you all I went through
the net to apply to send
a beach on days luck and fate in the fishes
he is dead though that blinking macro
Now that was five. Zero zero
I can tell you as I live life
a bit that these many years. I got. Easy
to Brady I would say you were wrong Mr
Sherlock Holmes was correct Good evening
Professor Mariotti welcome home and I mean
having destruction for being anybody you
know we by as for me they had while I watch
I would disguise by the way it fooled
them completely of course it didn't fool
me I never intended that the church I
meant only that it should bring us
face to face. Does not I don't tire is
a battle of wits disappearing into lakes
I may say I've been expecting you just I
made all but your precious Dr Dobelle
and his coat Oh yes and he's cold
but valuable your doctor and he's put out
of my business I think my main interest
is
a fair chance it gives me the
battle with you again money
out of it this is no simple
crime that you contemplate It's
a staggering blow against your own country
it doesn't concern me overly I should
make great
a profit from this affair and all my other
adventures put together then you refuse
all most assuredly. In fact I intend to
ensure the success of this venture tonight
by liquidating you stop us I think that
is the American phrase quite You were the
one man intelligent enough
to stand in my way. Oh come
now this is not the professor not be out
here the master criminal I once knew I
ducked record do as much to do think I
was going to shoot you Mr Holmes. Do you
know me no this is simply to prevent
a trouble subsea I expected you
and made from arrangements.
You see my goodness to homes these
shows lift out and you will rest
somewhat on
a comfortably in the false bottom of the
sea chest my sailor friend Jack Brady goes
to see immediately once out of sight
of land he pushes the chest overboard
time up. To have your
good friend Dr Watson
telling title this adventure the end of
Sherlock Holmes he will be disappointed if
he intended to call it the end of
Professor Mariotti. How it was.
That it will.
Bring in man show like Holmes
Too bad he was on it's just.
The one naked man it takes Mr Holmes
writer that carpenter shop and next on the
door
a man comes out and and in they go thank
you George we took over the watch got that
good night. Because Mr was able to
accomplish but these are scary he hopes to
frighten money into Russian Cobell into
another hiding place the Archies
good idea to cap the leak.
Just
a bit to say that they're asking me out
Scott after mug shot in the fight.
They are government Jack Brady ship's
company ship matter might look on boy
destination unknown McNally
as it may be testable making.
Right now. See yourself.
There should be a doctor just
a couple of simple see very many where
I get over that thank you come.
On that I. Could not or should.
Go get was a lot of nonsense I don't
understand that thing was when
a ton of those men staggering
in for jobs up into
a few pools you take that much energy if
you just look at the time on the top it
might be
a false bottom I know
you're stuck there. In
a.
White compound where
nobody. You know that.
You need to yell at them so abruptly
drop me on my head oh my God I've been
delighted some professional
Moriarty's other live in
a position about to talk about coke no going
back and what I'm going to do with I'm
going to watch this focused on my face and
I'm going to Miss Emily again I've got
to find some clue to the content of October's
message Come on quick. I only got one
time so I know if I was preparing it he
was seated at this desk you know he was
sitting on the couch when he was the message
of the envelope here the message was
written in this pen you know he
used to pass on this one thank you.
It was this writing then yes has it been
used since you know. He should be here
and must be here what was different then
this pencil is hot enough to make an
impression on the cross fibers in which
this paper is made. Impressions of the
moment. Oh invisible if
we most of the sheet in
a solution of progress insults drive it
and then photograph it I'll talk about it
like the fibers broken but the writing will
absorb less of this emotion than other
parts of the paper. Switch
off the lights Watson.
Replaced the slide in the
projector turn on the light the
broken fibers appear dark of the rest
of the paper and are therefore visible
splendored home now I recognize that code
humor case we had some years ago it's
probably the same alphabet substitution
code is what I believe Dr Toby Allman to
communicate with us but that means just use
of the alphabet I don't understand one
of the oldest continuous is based
on the repetition of figures he has
a letter most usually produced language
therefore the figure most huge probably in
this message is E T O O I am
following that order frequency
you mean you can believe these figures as
if they were not as of the outer limits
of my disabler give me one minute
and you shall have the message
and what is the message Watson this photo
but almost been putting our legs so
a lot of jibberish. Do you know M T
H K We like an eye doctors chart
doctor took it as a brilliant scientist I
saw immediately that he wouldn't send us
a message so simple to decipher neither
would he have fixed top figures without
a meeting the nutrition Telford
substitution code is it is Watson but with
a very clever variation you see the one
two three figures means that we skip
letters not all that in other words observe
Watson. The first letter which is I
skips one becomes J. The second letter Y.
Skips two and becomes
a and the third skips three
and becomes C J C J S C O
B D U R R E R J could do it
it's misandrist and to end
up back to the house P A. A C E
C R E S status question right I
said Holmes this mad dog I must
be important obviously Watson he must have
some connection with the bangs I'd want
to build wouldn't have taken so much trouble
to see that I got his name to Congress
message J O S E P H Joseph.
M D D I A C M A phone doesn't make it
a sentence you must have
used some other variations.
Phone names and addresses you could do it
a professor panel Dr Kern and this fourth
infernal cipher which doesn't fit the
code Christmas box is
what. I'm beginning to see the plan. Not
to talk about the budget is bombs I had
into four parts just as we brought it back
from Switzerland he's giving one section
of the mechanism to each of
these famous scientists What
a fascinating plan you see each plant
is useless without the other three and
undoubtedly none of these scientists is
known to each other professor Mariotti also
has the code and we must allow for his
ability to decipher it we haven't time to
break the pop code now we must get to the
first are you going to point out you
don't spell US question first right I'm
going to text you very very carefully
return Thank you.
You know what are you going to take a
girl of you know yes but there's been
a bit of trouble so you can't go in this
particular strugglers well to monitor just
to show Coach hold starters.
There it is
a door. Mr Rose How did you know about this
the other New York fifteen minutes ago
we've been out of homes there's still time
to see family to make but some of this
time found on kind of good
to what deductions and
a mystery affects inspector facts but
how do you know about them I mean to my
dad Watson this man has been dead for
thieves two was obvious and wasting the
time and I know this is destructive
probably on America to.
You know anything about two men
named federal income found only.
Poorly came in two seconds before I telephoned
one if we can do Holmes and how he's
going to big stuff and he's got the code
now this Watson Scotland Yard reports two
murders that makes three in all but the
before boxes and four codes obviously my
God has broken the fault code.
Writers the name of the fourth man thank
goodness for the book what is the name of
the fourth man. Or what is the
name of the farm man I don't know.
Oh well I just I mean the
fourth man we're going to.
Have to go. Oh don't you realize what
this means for Agent we not only lose the
tool belt bombsite ourselves but Germany
gets it country plus London not to mention
noted you know all over again but with ten
times the effect. Don't you suppose I
realize that's Reginald and disposer give
my life to code the last man in that
message must be some solution and actually
wants him removed I need to do it I'm
only in conflict in
a moment all these little some figures
well into my brain for pretty.
Twisted around. Thank you that's what
Christians around you said so simple I never
thought of it reverse the
slight. You see don't
these figures are not identical with the
first three names in other words all the
figures of name number Paul are written
backwards and we can write do it until be
reversed the slide when they read correctly
from left to right. Let's work on it
that's
a lot simpler. But. Why would Dr till
Bell want to reverse the figures
of number four and added precaution was
drug against the site I should point of the
wrong hands. Quite
a compliment to you Mr Evans I mean are
told they were taking for granted did you
would recognise the difference
thank you. Yeah far the.
I C K H O F F M E.
S O A N E S Q. Some Square
we just leave it once but
a minute. Information
will you please give me the address above
Frederic Hof not in Sloane Square I break
this code. I'll find the name of
that fourth man before hold it out.
There is not much more time for submariners
to pick us up off Seamus and six hours
beaten home so far we'll meet
a confounded submarine with
a bomb inside intact but told
Belle is unconscious again. As
a last resort we could abandon the code in
toto better Johnny it tried to Bella get
in here. Late
spilling a glass of water with a
very fortunate accident might be
a street brought up the doctor took
a version of the site I was so simple that
it fooled us I was looking for something
ingenious this easy to get us
he simply reversed the cipher.
And. He. Sees. I see
K H O N. And. In.
This and of
a. Hofner snowmen Square.
Have told us. That would
be the perfect seal
a kick in their nirvana us to take and
or hope no no we can use Hoffa is
a brilliant scientist if Dr Dobelle doesn't
recover from your to sweeten Hofner
will be able to get the Pol Pot's to get
you one got people call him hot I do will
bring him here with the fault
section of the bomb site how to.
Put up your hands Professor Hoffman.
Going. Up to the box.
In.
The hand you need again Professor.
Sherlock Holmes. An improvement on
the other make up and things up as
a so you think you've beaten
me Holmes I have. Rio off nice
safe in the hands of Scott and God But
I still have to build now I will sell
Germany the inventor instead of the invention
you have learned nothing from him in
spite of all your torture and eyes you
wouldn't be trying so desperately to collect
the four sections of the bomb site I can
observe nation my deal. But observe
further that you are now in my hands and
I have profited by my loss mistake of
allowing underlings to attain to you.
Almost took my place and might it not to
spare you side with him he
instructed me to attach
a small plate of I'm going to he's
a Briton fellow Holmes I helped
him prepare the operators to do
a little adopted that is I put in luminous
paint when he told me to very clear my
Dr Watson the operator's rips at regular
intervals leave you trail of luminous
paint I see leading us to
Mariotti and mystery of.
Why it was a confident Professor only
a suggestion but how do you know that
Scotland Yard isn't waiting to break in at
this bit of moment I selected this address
could special care no one can find it
not even Scotland Yard relax
Mr Holmes there's no escape
and I suddenly deaf to the window make
it open and shut opens up by that I will
pass as by the glass in the windows unbreakable
and the room is soundproof this is
my stronghold home equipped with
all them blocking conveniences of
a successful man in my profession because.
They faded out again saying.
I don't understand. It
Stop. Then it started. Not
stopped again maybe the operators broke
down always adjusting gentleman at
a crossroad back there
a comet have gone over the spot some paint
pick some up on the tiles and left this
post trail that's just what I was about
to suggest myself but it would try to.
Now tell me what you to be a gas
chamber the kind of hemp luck or just
a simple bullet through your brain
you disappoint me Professor he'd.
Yes. Somehow I always
thought that in the end you
proved to be just an ordinary cut throat
you know me better homes gas poison
boots I'll show you Professor when our
positions reversed I should have something
more colorful more imaginative to offer I
am satisfied to be the winner I shall be
a life I live is the without no part of
the last analysis I slip proved the more
resourceful man you didn't trap me here I
came here because I wanted to to prevent
your getting caught and all you can do in
return is to commit or remove to relieve
your sense of frustration and what my
good Mr Holmes could you have can see it
would have been so much more colorful
well even Offhand I can improve upon your
suggestions considerably the best in the
natural course and what is this brilliant
idea of yours you know that
a man dies he loses five pints of blood
as of course you do I should have you
placed on an operating table inject
a needle into your veins and slowly draw
off your life's blood the needle to the
last
a home slowly drop by drop the blood would
be drawn from nobody. You would be aware
of every explicit second video and
you would be watching yourself die
scientifically know to get
a reaction and in full possession
of the effect is interesting
isn't it I humbly submit professor that
to the very end I've been motor sauce for
than yourself you've played into
my hands to shut up ohms time
and again I've used this place as a
group of friends of mine injured in
a lot occasions with Scotland Yard. I had
a fully cooked hospital get. The
trail goes this way inspected.
Up by drop. Drop by.
In no way I'm almost sorry you want us
to meet and influence to me. But it was
obvious that I should leave. You
never moments now take Cobell
down to the boat stop the engine.
Closer to the end home. Closer and.
Second a few more on
drops leave you a D.C.
Keep body. And. You can feel them.
You're perfectly conscious and you
home National very conscious. Long
dead mariachi. Stillness same old
swaggering conceited Shylock
Holmes.
White. Mariotti as
a shot he'll kill it alludes to
keep an eye on the boat and make
a move to Dr Watson Oh I get
inside understand your way to
a professor often are conducted.
This way. While we are citizens via.
I coming in on the homes.
That have to give
a career to my friend. Which
is only the coup de gras.
Do you want your home. In the
country Inspector my men
outside that you were done
for really. Just take
a look at the Winter. And see C.S.M.
.
Finest if you want go long term. But it.
Is Dr Joe Bell expect to eat too badly it
thank heavens for that look after him you
have taken to the car.
In much to get you but not in my revolver
You realize of course when I was brought
into the room blindfolded I heard the
mechanism of this door was and yet knowing
that I said if you plan to swear to state.
That accepting To me suicide My dear
professor that all my deal is you this is
not an ordinary as it were. My mistake.
It is basically well prepared as the
rest of my humble quarters I have
a trap set electric eye principle my
passing through will break the beat and
automatically open the high deceptive trap
door. Behind me of course my pursuit I
mean you might be
a home we're going to be problems sixty
feet into the sewers below homes.
For money ot. I neglected to why didn't you
seem some careless person can of course
is trapped go Mr dokey. Among whites and.
Germany wanted the job site
will send them an audio played.
Yes thanks to Mr Sherlock
Holmes. And to Mrs Toby. And up
close and Speck and. That's all I miss.
Things are looking up. The supply
lines still on the map yes.
This is
a fortress. So. There's less of. This
this really. This.